Hello everyone welcome to this channel.  This video
is related to ICICI LBD General Insurance Company Limited.  ICICI LBD General Insurance
Company Limited has declared its final dividend
for investors along with the quarterly results for the financial year 2025.
What is the record date for this final dividend?
And how has the company's performance been?
You will know the complete details including record date in this video.  So now let us know in detail about
this final dividend and the
financial results of the company.  ICICI LBD
General Insurance Company Limited
in its board meeting has recommended a
final dividend of ₹7 per share for the financial year 2024-25.  The
total dividend for the full year will be
₹12.50 per share.  This dividend will be
paid to eligible investors after the approval of shareholders in the upcoming Annual General Meeting (AGM) of the company.  The
record date for this final dividend has not been fixed yet.  The
company also announced
audited financial results for the fourth quarter and full year of the financial year.  The
Board approved these results on the recommendation of the Audit Committee.
ICICI Low LBA General Insurance
Company reported a 2% decline in profit for the March quarter at ₹
99 crore compared to ₹520 crore in the same quarter last year, according to a regulatory filing.
However, the
company's profit for the full financial year 2025 increased by 31% to
₹58 crore.  Which was
₹1919 crore in FY 2024.  If we look at the performance of the stock,
this stock has increased by 8% in one month.  Whereas the
stock has fallen by 14% in the last 6 months.  The
stock has gained 11% in the last one year.
However, the
stock has returned more than 66% in the last 2 years.   The
audit reports have been issued by Joint Statutory
Auditors PKF Sridhar & Santhanam LLP
and Walker Chandak & Co. LLP without
any changes.  The appointment of
MS Pareek & Associates as Secretarial Auditor for 5 years will be
placed for approval in the AGM.  The board
also approved allotment of 18 lakh stock options and 10 lakh stock units under ICICI Lombard's employee stock option schemes.
With this dividend announcement,
ICICI LBD has once again reiterated its
commitment to strong returns and transparency for investors.  The
52 week high of ICICI LBD General Insurance Company share
is ₹2302 and 52 week low is
₹147.  Face value of ICICI LBA General Insurance Company
share is ₹10